Enemy speed , eight.
Angle on the bow, sixty.
Angle to bow, sixty. Mark is set.
-Depth is set.
-Ran0e, five hundred .
Five hundred .
Within firing range.
Set torpedo speed , thirty-five knots.
Spread shots from tubec one and four.
Tubes one and four are ready.
Ready...
-Fire!
Torpedoes launched.
Five, four, three...
two, one.
Contact.
-Yes!
Great shot, Captain.
Yes, gentlemen .
We broke their back, gentlemen .
Fast screws! Bearing 1 -8-0!
A destroyer!
Down to ninety metres quickly!
Both motors full ahead !
AIl hands forward .
-Seal torpedo hatches!
-Starboard rudder, twenty!
Starboard rudder, twenty.
Check all hull openings!
Come about.
Passing 20Ü degrees.
Forty-five metres. Fast dive, Captain.
Both hydroplanes, please.
-Bearing?
-Steady at 22Ü degrees.
Contact drawin0 right.
Port en0ine stop.
Port engine stopped .
-Port engine half back.
Depth chargec!
Hold on .
The Tommies are crapping all over us.
Careful , that's fuel Ieaking !
Stop that Ieak!
She's dropped to 1 20 metres, Captain!
Blow all tanks! Surface! Surface!
Everythin0 clear! Lookouts to the bridge!
Diesel room , answer me!
I need a damage report, Hans!
They're all dead , Captain .
AII our mechanics.
The Chief Mechanic, the fat kid ,
the whole engine crew. All dead .
Port exhaust hatch broke.
Port diesel is flooded .
Crankcase is full of seawater.
-Starboard diesel . . .
-Seized two days a9o.
-What about my batteries?
-Damaged .
30Ü amps bow, 2Ü0 stern .
It's useless!
We have only enough power
to dive and maybe manoeuvre.
Thank you, Hans.
Pass the word to conserve electricity.
-Radioman !
-Captain?
To Berlin .
Location 85-32.
Diesel engines out. Electric motors only.
Send help.
I understand your family
comes from Koblenz.
Good Rhine farming folk.
You understand me, Mr Wentz?
Can you cpeak passable German?
Can you read and write it?
Or are you just a farm boy
with a German name?
I am just a farm boy.
One who can read ,
write and speak quite well .
I studied German at Brown University
before joining the war.
Thank you, Wentz.
Okay, Chief. Let's give it a test.
You said you could repair engines?
Captain , I apprenticed in my
uncle's gara9e, fixing scooters.
I need a mechanic!
What are they caying, Captain?
They want to be our guests.
I mpossible. Shoot them .
Standing orders of the Führer.
We will not pick up any survivors.
If they are found, they will report
our position with much eagerness.
Get on with it.
Our comrades have brought us fresh eggs,
bananas and even our mail .
Ahoy!
Ahoy! Welcome.
Have we got a job for you .
Which of you are the mechanics?
We're all mechanics.
And we're all very skilled .
We'll have you underway before dawn .
Ahoy!
Who wants this junk?
Pornography and dirty letters
stinking of French perfume.
A cack of pure shit.
I should throw it overboard .
Come!
Come on!
Welcome aboard .
AIarm!
Repel boarders! Alarm dive!
FIood all the tanks! Flood all the tanks!
Let's drown these vermin ! Move your arses!
Faster!
My job?
Electrician . I am an electrician .
Hello, 9entlemen .
Give us a hand with the lines.
Yes, 0ladly.
What are they doing?
Something'c wrong .
Go back!
-Go back! Go back!
-Go back!
Back to the ship!
Get to the forward 0un!
They're firing on us.
Who, sir?
The cubmarine.
They've blown up our radio tower!
Short Intervals.
Prepare charges!
Set depth at 25.
Release chargec!
They fired a torpedo!